Ethan Aquilina

Spokane, WA | +1 (760) 586-8425 | quinn.ethan7@gmail.com

Career Summary

Very good at working with others and being able to connect and socialize with customers. I can work well with other team members and be a team player. Interacting with customers to provide a professional yet friendly experience is something I enjoy and am good at. I work very hard at learning and getting up to speed with whatever task is required of me and needs to be done; it would not take long for me to learn complex tasks. I'm versatile and adaptable to a position or role that is needed. I am a hard worker, very good with people/team members, and a quick learner.

Experience

Poll Worker, California | November 2018 | 1 Day

- Understand the proper steps to vote thoroughly and quickly to explain to citizens voting.
- Worked well with team members and helped them when needed.
- Arrived early in the morning to prep stations in a timely manner.
- Provided citizens with clear instructions on how to cast their votes.
- Provide a friendly environment so people would feel welcome and happy.
- Completed complex tasks such as organized ballots and votes to ensure none would mix and be lost.

Jersey Mike's Subs | June 2019 - Aug 2019 | 3-4 Days Weekly, Part Time

- Greeted and socialized with customers as they waited in line for food so they could feel engaged and have an enjoyable experience.
- Showed up consistently and on time for early morning preps and stocking.
- Efficiently prepared and made food until opening
- Provided consistently thorough and clean spaces. Including grill, fridge, and sink.
- Answered any specific and general questions about the menu or store in a friendly and professional manner.
- Created a positive and friendly environment around co-workers and customers.
- Work at the cash register quickly and effectively.

IT Inventory Manager, Walla Walla University | Nov 2020 - June 2021 | 3-4 Days Weekly, Part Time

- Navigated complicated programs that tracked school inventory to make revisions and check for errors in data.
- Close attention to detail while marking and tracking school inventory and adding it to existing data.
- Worked with others to effectively communicate updates and changes to the inventory.
- Listened effectively to quickly learned complicated instructions to effectively use and operate computers and computer programs.

ASG Outdoor Programmer, Spokane Falls Community College | Nov 2022 - June 2023 | 3-4 Days Weekly, Part Time

- Worked and communicated effectively with a team to run events.
- Brainstormed and planned events for the school to enjoy.
- During events, I regularly checked to make sure students were enjoying their time.
- Frequently interacted and communicated with students.

- Created a fun and welcoming environment at events.
- Balanced school effectively with a busy schedule of events.

Education

Escondido Adventist Academy | High School Diploma/GED Spokane Falls Community College | Currently pursuing bachelor's in Computer Science

Skills

Industry Knowledge: Inventory Management, Restocking, Food & Grill, Cash Handling

Technical Skills: Typing, IOS, Windows, Computers, Computer Components

Soft Skills: Socializing, maintaining engaging conversations, People skills, Friendly, Organization, Communication,

Attention to Detail, Multi-Tasking, Customer/Member Etiquette, Phone Etiquette, Conflict Resolution